wanderingeducators.com 2015-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Wandering Educators

At wanderingeducators.com ("WE"), we strive to develop and present innovative 

products and services to benefit our users and registered users (("Members"). We 

recognize that privacy is an important issue, so we design and operate our products 

and services with your privacy in mind. This wanderingeducators.com Privacy Policy 

outlines the types of personal information we may collect when you use our service 

("Service"), which is described in greater detail in the Terms of Service ("TOS"), 

available at <http://www.wanderingeducators.com/terms-service.html>, as well as some of the steps 

we take to secure it.

**  
What this policy covers**

****  
Your privacy is very important to us. This page will show our firm commitment to your

privacy. This policy covers how we treat personal information that we may collect or 

receive from you when you use our service. "Personal information" is information 

about you that is personally identifiable, such as your social security number, name, 

address, name, address, email address, or phone number.

wanderingeducators.com will not sell, loan, rent, lease, barter, or publish your 

personal information to a third party. All data that we keep on you is kept strictly for 

wanderingeducators.com business use, to assist you in your current or future 

purchases or in analyzing sales trends. No customer data is stored on servers that are 

accessible to the internet. All data is downloaded and deleted from our internet 

server several times a day.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies and/or other entities that 

WE does not own or control, to people that are not managed or employed by WE, 

and/or to operators of sites which are linked to or from wanderingeducators.com

**  
Data and Information Collection and Use**

**  
General**

WE collects information from and about you when you register with WE as a 

member, and when you use WE's service.

Users who visit WE's site and do not register do not need to provide any personal 

information. WE does, however, collect limited, non-personally identifying 

information from non-registered users that browsers make available whenever a user 

visits a website. This information includes your internet protocol (IP) address, browser 

type, browser language, cookies, and use patterns.

When you register as a Member, we ask for personal information from you, which 

may include your name, email address, date of birth, gender, zip code, personal 

interested, and a password. Your password will be maintained on our system in an 

encrypted form and you will be able to create a unique username that will identify 

you during login and when you are using the service. Please note that WE owns your 

username, grants you a license to use it while you are a Member, and reserves all 

rights to your username once you either cease to be a Member or following an 

extended period of inactivity, including but not limited to the right to revoke, reuse, 

resell, or license your username.

Certain members may opt to particiapte in programs offered by WE where a 

member can earn WE Marketplace dollars. If you participate in such programs, WE 

may require you to provide additional information, including but not limited to your 

social security number. All such information will be maintained in secure and 

encrypted areas of our system.

Once you register with WE and sign into our site, you are not anonymous to us.

WE uses the information collected for the following purposes: to customize the 

advertising and content that you see, to fulfill requests for products and service, to 

improve our service, to contact you, to conduct research, and to provide 

anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.  
 **  
Publishing on wanderingeducators.com**

Use care when posting personal information or personal content on our Service, 

particularly sensitive information such as social security numbers, financial 

information, home addresses, or phone numbers.

You should be aware that, when you post information in WE, the information that 

you post - including but not limited to the content of the post, header information, 

username, and email address associated with the posting - may be read, copied, 

used, and redistributed by people you do not not. 

The contents of the postings that you submit to the service are stored and 

maintained on our servers in order to publish the postings and provide the service. in 

order to protect our Members from email harvesting software and bots, we attempt 

to "mask" email addresses so that they are typically human readable but not 

machine readable. In addition, we collect and maintain information about your 

account activity, such as the contents of your posts, the links that you click on, 

search inquiries, postings that you comment upon, and your preferred settings when 

using the service.

**  
Children**

To comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, the service is only 

available to users and Members who are at least 13 years old. If you are under 13, 

you may NOT use wanderingeducators.com. 

WE needs to ask all users, including children under the age of 13, for certain personal 

information that is reasonably necessary to determine the user's eligibility to 

participate on and belong to the site.

**  
Contests**

WE runs contests on our site in which we may ask visitors for contact information 

(typically, the user's email address) and demographic information (i.e., zip code, 

age, or income level). WE will never disclose this information; it is only used to 

provide contact information for the winners, and demographic data for our contest 

sponsors.

At times, WE will run contests that will require a written entry, in the form of an 

"article," i.e., a story for the funniest travel stories contest. These written entry contests 

will be judged anonymously by published authors, photographers, and/or educators, 

and said prizes will be awarded to the winner(s).

At times, WE will run contests for increasing membership. All members who 

participate in such contests will have their results tallied by an independent 

organization, and contact informatio used only to award prize(s) to the winner(s).

**  
Information Sharing and Disclosure**

WE does not rent, sell, share, or otherwise disclose personal information about you 

with other people or non-affiliated companies, except to provide products or 

services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following 

circumstances:

a. WE may provide information to trusted partners who work on our behalf and who 

have entered into confidentiality agreemens with us.  
b. WE responds to valid subpoenas, court orders, and other legal proceedings. We 

also may disclose information if we deem it necessary to exercise our own legal rights 

or to defend ourselves against legal claims.  
c. WE will share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding 

illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical 

safety of any person, violations of our TOS, or as otherwise required by state or federal 

law.  
d. WE may transfer information about you if we are acquired or merged with another 

company.

**  
Financial Information Security**

Financial information that is collected by wanderingeducators.com is only used to 

bill the member for products and services ordered through the WE Marketplace.

You can enter your credit card number on a secure (https) form and transmit the 

form over the internet to a secure server without risk of an intermediary obtaining 

your credit card information. The security features offered by your web browser 

technology protects commercial transactions, as well as all other communications, 

from misappropriation and fraud that could otherwise occur as information passes 

through internet computers.

With SSL implemented on both the client and server, your internet communications 

are transmitted in encrypted form. Information you send can be trusted to arrive 

privately and unaltered to the server you specify (and no other).

SSL uses authentication and encryption technology. For example, your browsers 

export implementation of SSL (U.S. government approved) uses a high-grade, 128-bit 

key size. The encryption established between you and a server remains valid over 

multiple connections, yet the effort expended to defeat the encryption of one 

message cannot be leveraged to defeat the next message.

Your browser and secure servers deliver server authenticatin using signed digital 

certificates issued by trusted third parties known as certificate authorities. A digital 

certificate verifies the connectino between a server's public key and the server's 

identification (as a driver's license verifies the connection between your photograph 

and your personal identification). Cryptographic checks, using digital signatures, 

ensure that information within a certificate can be trusted. 

You know that you have a secure connection when you look at the location (URL) 

field. If the URL begins with https:// (instead of http://), the document comes from a 

secure server. To connect to an HTTP server that provides security using the SSL 

protocol, insert the letter "s" so that the URL begins with https://. You need to use 

https:?? for HTTP URLs with SSL and http:// for HTTP URLs without SSL.

You can also verify the security of a webpage by examining the security icon in the 

bottom left corner of your browser window.

Only your computer and the server can encrypt and decrypt your information. In 

transit, the information is an unreadable mess. An intermediary can route the data, 

and even copy it, but the information cannot be de-encrypted, and thus remains 

private and safely communicated.

**  
Information Security**

WE takes appropriate physical and electronic measures to protect against 

unauthorized access to, alteration of, and disclosure of personal information.

Access to personal information is limited to employees who need to know that 

information in order to successfully provide our service. All our employees enter into 

confidentiality agreements with WE.

**  
Cookies**

WE may set and access "cookies" on your computer. A "cookie" is a small file, 

containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a 

website. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, target advertising, 

and to better understand how our members interact with us. We do this by storing 

user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how you use 

our service. Most browsers are set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser 

to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent, but this will impact 

the quality and speed of your user experience on the site.

**  
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Account Information**

You may edit your personal profice and related personal information at any time by 

visiting your account at wanderingeducators.com

You may delete your member account by sending an email to 

**  
Changes to this Policy**

WE may update and change this Policy from time to time.  
All updates and changes will be posted to this webpage.  
We will notify you directly if we make significant changes to this Privacy Policy.
